Saihajvir Gill

Information

Address 6701 125 Street Surrey, BC V3W 1N7 Canada

Phone 604–442–2841

Email saihajvir@hotmail.com

Skills

Ability to take initiative and further my understanding of topics on my own

Strong leadership

Excellent reliability and punctuality

Understand business goals and how to achieve them

Able to provide and receive constructive criticism

Completely fluent in English and Punjabi

Profile

Currently a graduating student from BCIT's Digital Design and Development program with a passion for front end development. Previously experienced working in fast paced retail environments focused on excellent service and communication.

Technical Skills

- Front End Development
- Using APIs to improve functionality
- Databasing
- UX/UI Design
- Wireframing and Prototyping
- Graphic Design

Tools

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React, Next.JS, React-Native
- Figma
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Visual Studio Code

Employment History

Specialist, Apple Store Guildford Town Centre

August 2021 — October 2021

- · Assist, educate, and guide customers through a product or purchase
- Maintain store and corporate visual/service standards
- Meet daily sales goals

Designated Sales Associate, Nordstrom Pacific Centre

March 2017 — August 2020

- Provided knowledgeable and thoughtful opinions and wardrobes for men
- Managed Men's Denim department, included looking after sales, stock and merchandising
- Trained new associates about men's denim and how to sell it
- Met personal sales goals and department sales goals

Education

Digital Design and Development, BCIT Burnaby

September 2020 — Present

- Developed websites and mobile apps using HTML, CSS, JS, NextJS, and React Native
- Experienced in UX/UI Design and Figma
- · Comfortable with Adobe programs such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere, and After Effects
- Used to working in both group and individual settings

High School, Tamanawis Secondary School

September 2011 — June 2016